http://www.completeplastics.com/privacy-policy

Cart
(0)
Shopping Cart
Your cart is empty!
Call Us Now (770) 427-3834
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy | Complete Plastic SystemsPart I:  Information CollectionComplete Plastics Systems, Inc. / Heat Tech Systems, Inc. collects information through our Web site at several points. We collect the following information about primary visitors:Internet Protocol (IP) AddressLocation of where the IP address originatedWhat pages of this Web site were visited?What link led the individual to this Web site?What page the individual left this Web site?What search engine term was used to find this Web site?We may also collect types of personally identifiable information which our users divulge about other people, such as referrals or gift purchases. Complete Plastics Systems, Inc. / Heat Tech Systems, Inc. does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 18 to divulge personal information. We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information:Internet Protocol (IP) AddressLocation of where the IP address originatedWhat pages of this Web site were visited?What link led the individual to this Web site?What page the individual left this Web site?What search engine term was used to find this Web site?We collect demographic data in order to determine where our Web site’s traffic is coming from and how people are finding us. We verify the accuracy of this information by using a free, online service that tracks this information. We collect this information through Google Analytics. The information is collected involuntarily and remains confidential. Other information we request is optional through a Web form that can be found on our Contact Us page.We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable Complete Plastics Systems, Inc. / Heat Tech Systems, Inc. to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies do not have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. Banner advertising and/or logos appearing on our Web site may collect information. Complete Plastics Systems, Inc. / Heat Tech Systems, Inc. is not responsible for how third parties collect any information following.Part II:  Information UsageThe information collected by Complete Plastics Systems, Inc. / Heat Tech Systems, Inc. will be used for Web site visiting tracking only. Users who provide information will receive notifications.Registered users will receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. The information we collect will not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources such as credit history to authorize purchases.We will not share data with any person, company or other government agency. We offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours. Our Web site offers blog sites. Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge. We retain the right to monitor, censor, edit and delete these blog site posts. If our policy on information collection or uses changes, we will advise you by posting the change on our home page.Part III:  Problem ResolutionIf problems arise, users may contact the Complete Plastics Systems, Inc. / Heat Tech Systems, Inc. by e-mailing us at sales@completeplastics.com. We are committed to resolving disputes within one business week.Part IV:  Data Storage and SecurityComplete Plastics Systems, Inc. / Heat Tech Systems, Inc. protects user information with SSL encryption when making donations and other technology and procedures used to protect consumer privacy.
PRIVACY POLICY - RETURN & REFUND POLICY
PARTS - ASSEMBLIES - EQUIPMENT - HEATERS - SLIDE PRODUCTS - ABOUT - CONTACT
Copyright © 2020. All rights reserved.
Complete Plastic Systems, Inc. ~ Heat Tech Systems, Inc.
2106 Moon Station Dr NW, Kennesaw, GA 30144
P: (770) 427-3834 | F: (770) 427-3932 | E: sales@completeplastics.com
Website design, maintenance and hosting by MarketPros
